tamu.edu 2007-06-30

# Texas A&M University - Privacy Statement

[About A&M

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/aboutam/index.html "About A&M")

[A&M Facts

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/aboutam/amfacts/index.html "About A&M")

[Administration

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/aboutam/adminam/ "Administration")

[Bush Library

](http://bushlibrary.tamu.edu/ "Bush Library")

[Campus Life

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/aboutam/campuslife/index.html "Campus Life")

[Diversity

](http://diversity.tamu.edu/ "Diversity")

[Giving to A&M

](http://giving.tamu.edu/ "Giving to A&M")

[Safety Hotline

](http://safetyhotline.tamu.edu/ "Safety Hotline")

[more

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/aboutam/index.html "more")

[Academics

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/academics/index.html "Academics")

[Colleges

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/academics/colleges.html "Colleges")

[Departments

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/academics/departments.html "Departments")

[Distance/Continuing Education

](http://www.tamu.edu/ode/choice "Distance/Continuing Education")

[Graduate Studies

](http://ogs.tamu.edu/ "Graduate Studies")

[Graduation

](http://graduation.tamu.edu/ "Graduation")

[Institutes

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/academics/institutes.html "Institutes")

[Libraries

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/academics/libraries.html "Libraries")

[more

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/academics/index.html "more")

[Admissions

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/admissions/index.html "Admissions")

[Admissions

](http://www.tamu.edu/admissions "Admissions")

[Distance Education

](http://www.tamu.edu/ode/disted "Distance Education")

[Financial Aid

](http://financialaid.tamu.edu/ "Financial Aid")

[Graduate Admissions

](http://www.tamu.edu/admissions/Grad "Graduate Admissions")

[Housing

](http://reslife.tamu.edu/ "Housing")

[International Programs Office

](http://international.tamu.edu/ "International Programs Office")

[Tuition & Fees

](http://finance.tamu.edu/sbs "Tuition & Fees")

[more

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/admissions/index.html "more")

[Athletics

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/amathletics/index.html "Athletics")

[Athletics

](http://www.aggieathletics.com/ "Athletics")

[Big 12 Conference

](http://www.big12sports.com/ "Big 12 Conference")

[Facilities

](http://aggieathletics.com/facilities.php "Facilities")

[Parking Information

](http://transport.tamu.edu/specialevents/sports.aspx "Parking Information")

[Recreational Sports

](http://recsports.tamu.edu/ "Recreational Sports")

[Ticket Information

](http://www.12thmanfoundation.com/tickets/ticketbox.asp "Ticket Information")

[12th Man Foundation

](http://www.12thmanfoundation.com/ "12th Man Foundation")

[more

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/amathletics/index.html "more")

[News

](http://www.tamu.edu/tamunews "News")

[A&M News

](http://www.tamu.edu/tamunews "A&M News")

[Agricultural Communications

](http://agnews.tamu.edu/ "Agricultural Communications")

[Athletics News

](http://www.aggieathletics.com/press.php "Athletic News")

[Engineering News

](http://engineeringnews.tamu.edu/ "Engineering News")

[The Battalion Online

](http://www.thebatt.com/home "The Battalion Online")

[University Calendars

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/academics/calendars.html "University Calendars")

[Marketing & Communications

](http://www.tamu.edu/marcomm/ "Marketing")

[more

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/amnews/index.html "more")

[Research

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/research/index.html "Research")

[Funding Opportunities

](http://opd.tamu.edu/funding-opportunities "Funding Opportunities")

[Graduate Studies

](http://ogs.tamu.edu/ "Graduate Studies")

[Proposal Development

](http://opd.tamu.edu/ "Proposal Development")

[Research Compliance

](http://researchcompliance.tamu.edu/ "Research Compliance")

[Research Park

](http://researchpark.tamu.edu/ "Research Park")

[Undergraduate Research

](http://ugr.tamu.edu/ "Undergraduate Research")

[Vice President for Research

](http://vpr.tamu.edu/ "Vice President for Research")

[more

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/research/index.html "more")

[Services

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/amservices/index.html "Services")

[Bookstore

](http://tamu.bkstore.com/ "Bookstore")

[Computing

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/amservices/computing.html "Computing")

[Employee Services

](http://employees.tamu.edu/ "Employee Services")

[Food

](http://food.tamu.edu/ "Food")

[Texas A&M Employment

](https://tamujobs.tamu.edu/ "Texas A&M Employment")

[Transportation

](http://transport.tamu.edu/ "Transportation")

[University Police

](http://www.tamu.edu/upd "University Police")

[more

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/amservices/index.html "more")

[Traditions

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/traditions/index.html "Traditions")

[Aggie Ring

](http://aggietraditions.tamu.edu/aggiering.shtml "Aggie Ring")

[Big Event

](http://bigevent.tamu.edu/ "Big Event")

[Bonfire Memorial

](http://www.tamu.edu/bonfirememorial/ "Bonfire Memorial")

[Muster

](http://muster.tamu.edu/ "Muster")

[Silver Taps

](http://aggietraditions.tamu.edu/silvertaps.shtml "Silver Taps")

[Traditions

](http://aggietraditions.tamu.edu/ "Traditions")

[12th Man

](http://aggietraditions.tamu.edu/12thman.shtml "12th Man")

[more

](http://www.tamu.edu/home/traditions/index.html "more")

[Home

](http://www.tamu.edu/ "Home") |   

Texas A&M University (TAMU) respects your privacy. The University's main Webpage does not collect personal information about visitors. In particular, we do not use "cookies" to collect information.

Personal information that you provide via e-mail or through other online means will be used only for purposes necessary to serve your needs, such as responding to an inquiry or other request for information. This may involve redirecting your inquiry or comment to another person or department better suited to meeting your needs.

We do, however, use server logs to collect information concerning your Internet connection and general information about your visit to our Web site. This information may be used to analyze trends; to create summary statistics for the purpose of determining technical design specifications; and to identify system performance or problem areas.

This means we sometimes acquire, record and analyze portions of the data that is entered into, stored on, and/or transmitted through this site by you. This information is only released -- when legally required -- to help law enforcement investigations, legal proceedings or internal investigations of TAMU rule and regulation violations. These groups would use the information to track the electronic interactions back to the source computer(s) or account(s). 

Some web pages at Texas A&M University may collect personal information about visitors and use that information for purposes other than those stated above. Each web page that collects information will have a separate privacy statement that will tell you how that information is used.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your use of this Web site, please contact the Webmaster or through regular mail at:

Texas A&M University  
Division of Marketing & Communications  
Attention: [Webmaster](mailto:webmaster@tamu.edu "Webmaster")  
202 Bizzell Hall East, MS 1372  
College Station, TX 77843-1372

COOKIES: A cookie file contains unique information that a Web site can use to track such things as passwords, pages you have visited, the date you last looked at a specific page, and to identify your session at a particular Web site.

SERVER LOG INFORMATION: The following information is collected from server logs for analysis

\- User/client hostname - The hostname (or IP address if DNS is disabled) of the user/client requesting access   
HTTP header, "user agent" - The user-agent information includes the type of browser, its version, and the operating system it is running on  
HTTP header, "referrer" - The referrer specifies the page from which the client accessed the current page   
System date - The date and time of the user/client request   
Full request - The exact request the user/client made Status - The status code the server returned to the user/client  
Content length - The content length, in bytes, of the document sent to the user/client  
Method - The request method used  
Universal Resource Identifier (URI) - The location of a resource on the server  
Query string of the URI - Anything after the question mark in a  
URI Protocol - The transport protocol and version used
